Recep Ahmet Saritekin

Mugla Sitki Kocman University Engineering Department Kotekli/Mugla

🛘 (+90) 537-247-9500 | 💌 rahmetsaritekin@gmail.com | 🖸 us | 🤡 saritekin | 📓 syny | 🛅 rahmetsaritekin | 💌 distortionalist

"We lay on our backs, looking at the ceiling and wondering what God had wrought when He made life so sad. Jack Kerouac-On The Road"

Summary_

During my high school life I became an semi-expert in the Wing-Tsun that is a traditional Southern Chinese Kung-fu styles in close range combat. I have played guitar and had a sing on my own and with many different music groups since high school. I have great interest in literature, philosophy, physics, mathematics and art. In general, I read, write, research and discuss. I'm traveling to Turkey, which is also the first goal with hitchhiking. I can stay on the road for a long time. My goal is not to arrive somewhere, I like the road itself, the blessings that the road offers me. Currently, I am a second grade computer engineering student at Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University. I've been learning new things by learning to learn for 3 years. I adopt free software philosophy. Previously, I was working as a full-stack developer and a blockchain developer. Now I'm doing research on machine learning and deep learning and we have a mechanic and electrician friend in our school and we are developing aircraft, rocket, dronestyle autonomous vehicles. I use Vim, jetbrains IDE's, jupyter notebook, linux and OSX in my work environment. I am someone who likes to solve problems in new ways and learn new technologies when needed.

Work Experience _____

Google Summer of Code <TensorFlow>

CA, United States

Nov. 2018, PRESENT

- May. 2019, 25 Aug. • I worked in the TensorFlow Dataset repository with Google Brain developers for 3 months.
- I added some new features, hunted bugs, reviewed pull requests, issues, etc.

Allonzi Istanbul, Turkey

CREATOR & SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

· A social app that guides people on their journey.

INOTEK Robotic AR-GE Mugla, Turkey

CREATOR & ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE RESEARCHER

Sep. 2017, PRESENT

- By collecting data from IOT devices in air, sea, air and forests, we need to determine the fire detection and so on.
- We are developing our own UAV (Unmanned Aerial Vehicle), drones and 3D printers.

Cryptouch Mugla, Turkey

CREATOR & BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Nov. 2017 - PRESENT

- Special communication application using blockchain and IPFS in infrastructure.
- · It has a distributed infrastructure focused on freedom, high security, scalability and permanency.
- Specific networks can be set up to certain people or individuals without external access.

Speakmates Tokyo, Japan

FREELANCER FULL STACK DEVELOPER & DJANGO DEVELOPER

Oct. 2017 - Jan. 2018

· A website that offers a platform where local or foreign language consultants and small groups of people who want to learn a foreign language can find each other and meet in comfortable places.

Honors & Awards

2018	Champion, Genç Beyinler Yeni Fikirler Idea Competition	Izmir, Turkey
2013	5nd , Ankara Ataturk Marathon Run	Ankara, Turkey
2010	Finalist, Turkey Futsal Tournament	İstanbul, Turkey
2009	Champion, Table Tennis City Tournament	Düzce, Turkey

DECEMBER 26, 2019 RECEP A. SARITEKIN · RESUME **Presentation**

Developer Conference Muğla, Turkey

SPEAKER < NEURAL NETWORKS AND DEEP LEARNING>

Nov. 2018

• I speak about basics of neural networks and modern deep learning applications.

Teknopark İzmir International Blockchain Workshop

SPEAKER < BLOCKCHAIN BASED SECURE COMMINICATION APPLICATION PROPOSAL: CRYPTOUCH>

• I speak about the advantages and business areas of my own project Cryptouch.

ISDFS 2018: 6th International Symposium on Digital Forensic and Security

SPEAKER < BLOCKCHAIN BASED SECURE COMMINICATION APPLICATION PROPOSAL: CRYPTOUCH>

• I explained my new project Cryptouch's security infrastructure in this conference.

Developer Conference Muğla, Turkey

SPEAKER <'TIR GIT> Feb. 2018

• I speak about GIT(the version control system) infrastructure, explained the whole documentation in this conference.

Education

Zeki ve White

MSKU (Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University Faculty of Engineering))

COMPUTER ENGINEERING UNDERGRADUATE EDUCATION Sep. 2017 - Exp. Aug. 2021

· I am trying to develop myself on the computer scienc by benefiting from the experiences of my teachers.

MSKU(Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University Faculty of Foreign Languages)

PREPARATORY EDUCATION Sep. 2016 - Aug. 2017

· I received a one-year preparatory education for 100% English Computer Engineering department.

Ankara Police Collage Ankara, Turkey

HIGH SCHOOL Sep. 2011 - Exp. Apr. 2015

• I was educated until the third year as the last students of the College(it's a high school). Then it was closed because of political reasons.

Extracurricular Activity

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL

· I am coming from metal guitar and I found a new friend who coming from classical guitar and we are create different taste improvisation musics that comes metal and classic touches and these are very absurd musics.

Dertsiz Deli

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL Jan. 2017 - PRESENT

· Together with my beautiful vocal, we try to mumbling little things and make music. We will share our musics in different social medias.

Düzce Anadolu Öğretmen High School Rock Band

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL Apr. 2015 - Jun. 2016

• We gave concerts at the festivals and graduations at high schools in Düzce.

Ankara Police College Wing Tsun Team

Ankara, Turkey **COACH ASSISTANT** Sep. 2012 - Apr.2015

• I would help the teacher during training, I would check and help my friends.

PKMG (Police College Rock Band)

SOLO GUITARIST & BACK VOCAL Oct. 2013 - Apr. 2015

· In the rock band of the school, I learned to be a team with my friends, to do something together and to produce new things.

- We attended the national high school music competition on behalf of our school.
- · We gave small concerts in different places.

Ankara Police College Athletics Team

Ankara, Turkey

Ankara, Turkey

Düzce, Turkey

İzmir, Turkey

Antalya, Turkey

Muğla, Turkey

Muğla, Turkey

May. 2018

Mar. 2018

MIDDLE DISTANCE AND FLAG RUNNER Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2013

· With our national instructor Adil and my friends, we participated in competitions and won prizes together for a year.

DECEMBER 26, 2019 RECEP A. SARITEKIN · RESUME